It'll scare the #2 out of you.
A Haunted House 2 is a comedy, horror film directed by Michael Tiddes.
After exorcising the demons of his ex, Malcolm starts afresh
with his new girlfriend and her two children.
After moving into their dream home, Malcolm is once
again plagued by bizarre paranormal events.
Malcolm, played by Marlon Wayans.
Megan, played by Jaime Pressly.
Kisha, played by Essence Atkins.
Miguel, played by Gabriel Iglesias.
Noreen, played by Missi Pyle.
Becky, played by Ashley Rickards.
A Haunted House 2 is a 2014 American horror comedy film directed by Michael Tiddes and starring Marlon Wayans, Jaime Pressly, Essence Atkins, Gabriel
Iglesias, Missi Pyle, Ashley Rickards, Affion Crockett, Steele Stebbins, Rick Overton, Hayes MacArthur, Dave Sheridan and Cedric the Entertainer.
The film is the sequel to the 2013 film A Haunted House.
Produced by IM Global Octane and distributed by Open Road
Films, the film was released on March 28, 2014.
The film received negative reviews from critics, and
earned over $25 million at the box office.
The film explores themes of exorcism, haunted
house, parody, paranormal, evil doll.
The tone is dark and lighthearted and emotional.